<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Exploring CS</title><link>https://blog.sidpatel.org/</link><description>Recent content on Exploring CS</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 12:04:39 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.sidpatel.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>My First Blog</title><link>https://blog.sidpatel.org/posts/helloworld/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 12:04:39 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blog.sidpatel.org/posts/helloworld/</guid><description>Starting my journey to become Software Developer Hi everyone, this is my very first post in my journey to become the Software Engineer/Developer. My educational background is in Mechanical and Industrial Engineering, but ever since I was in the undergraduate school, I was fascinated with the computers. After I finished the undergraduate, I went to pursue a graduate degree in Industrial and Systems Engineering.
I worked as a Product Engineer for a Manufacturing Company for almost 5 years after graduating from college, but my interest in the computer programming remains.</description></item><item><title>Pizza-N-Go - A Full-stack Application</title><link>https://blog.sidpatel.org/portfolios/pizza-n-go/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 14:04:51 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blog.sidpatel.org/portfolios/pizza-n-go/</guid><description>I would admit, the picture above looks delicious, isn&amp;rsquo;t it ?
I like to present the food ordering application I have created to learn Full-stack Web Development. I had general understanding of the web application and how they are built, but I always wanted to build one from ground up with some of the advance features like real time communication using Web Sockets, user Sessions and Cookie management, integrating text message API, asynchronous operations and more.</description></item></channel></rss>