<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Portfolios on Exploring CS</title><link>https://blog.sidpatel.org/portfolios/</link><description>Recent content in Portfolios on Exploring CS</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 14:04:51 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.sidpatel.org/portfolios/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pizza-N-Go: A Full-stack Application</title><link>https://blog.sidpatel.org/portfolios/pizza-n-go/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 14:04:51 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blog.sidpatel.org/portfolios/pizza-n-go/</guid><description>I would admit, the picture above looks delicious, isn&amp;rsquo;t it ?
I like to present the food ordering application I have created to learn Full-stack Web Development. I had general understanding of the web application and how they are built, but I always wanted to build one from ground up with some of the advance features like real time communication using Web Sockets, user Sessions and Cookie management, integrating text message API, asynchronous operations and more.</description></item><item><title>Interview-Scheduler: A React application</title><link>https://blog.sidpatel.org/portfolios/react-scheduler/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 14:04:51 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blog.sidpatel.org/portfolios/react-scheduler/</guid><description>React scheduler with up to five appointments per day. A dynamic and a true single-page application that utilizes various React hooks and states. This app utilizes asynchronous programming and testing tools like Jest for unit testing and integration testing and cypress.io for end-to-end testing.
You can find this application running live on React-Interview-Scheduler 🗓️.
Once you open the applicaiton, you may need to wait for three - four seconds or reload to fully load the app.</description></item><item><title>Job-Comparator: An Android Application</title><link>https://blog.sidpatel.org/portfolios/job-comparator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 14:04:51 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blog.sidpatel.org/portfolios/job-comparator/</guid><description>Introduction Job Comparison App is an Android mobile app which allows a user to compare job offers using customizable settings.
System requirements Job Comparison App requires Android version 10 (Android Q) and Pixel 4 XL.
Features and functionalities Main menu When the app starts, a main menu is displayed and it allows the user to choose one of the four options:
Enter or edit current job details Enter job offers Adjust the comparison settings Compare job offers (enabled if there are 2 or more jobs).</description></item></channel></rss>