<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Posts on Exploring CS</title><link>https://blog.sidpatel.org/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Exploring CS</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 14:50:46 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.sidpatel.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Two Sum</title><link>https://blog.sidpatel.org/posts/two-sum/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 14:50:46 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blog.sidpatel.org/posts/two-sum/</guid><description>Hey guys,
I am going to start posting the solutions for some of the coding exercise I am solving through Leetcode. If you are preparing for the tech interviews, I would definitely reccommend this resource.
It may seems intimidating first, but start with the easy problems. If you get stuck on particular problem, then see the solution and understand the approach/pattern in it and then try to solve it yourself again from your understanding.</description></item><item><title>Linked List</title><link>https://blog.sidpatel.org/posts/linked-list/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 10:14:42 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blog.sidpatel.org/posts/linked-list/</guid><description>Overview So you might be wondering, what is this Linked List data structure is ? I will try to explain it in easy to understand fashion.
You must be already familiar with the term ‘data structure’. Data structure are how we store the data. In most modern programming languages, some data structures come in-built. For example, array or hash map etc. We need to decide which data structure we need to use as per our use case.</description></item><item><title>My First Blog</title><link>https://blog.sidpatel.org/posts/helloworld/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 12:04:39 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blog.sidpatel.org/posts/helloworld/</guid><description>Starting my journey to become Software Developer Hi everyone, this is my very first post in my journey to become the Software Engineer/Developer. My educational background is in Mechanical and Industrial Engineering, but ever since I was in the undergraduate school, I was fascinated with the computers. After I finished the undergraduate, I went to pursue a graduate degree in Industrial and Systems Engineering.
I worked as a Product Engineer for a Manufacturing Company for almost 5 years after graduating from college, but my interest in the computer programming remains.</description></item></channel></rss>